Guide to the Gerard Malanga Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- September 2006 acquisition, 1906-2005; 81.05; (102 boxes) + 2 art, 6 rolls, 4 broadside folders
  - Photocopy delineation, undated (Box 91 (Oversize))
  - Bennington exhibition material, undated; 5 (Box 91 (Oversize))
  - "Artwork Components: Robert Moses: From an Irretrievable Past", circa 1987 (Box 91 (Oversize))
  - "'The Cooler': Announcement Cards / Ticket Stubs /Flyers...", undated; 2 (Box 92 (Oversize))
  - "GM: Press Clippings", 1960s-1980s; 2 (Box 92 (Oversize))
  - Printed material, 1997, undated; 2 (Box 92 (Oversize))
  - "Cover Art Research for This Will Kill That ", circa 1983 (Box 93 (Oversize))
  - Berkshire photographs, undated (Box 93 (Oversize))
  - "Jane Birkin Self-portrait", 1985 (Box 93 (Oversize))
  - Photographs of Lita Hornick by Allen Ginsberg, 1992, 1995 (Box 93 (Oversize))
  - "Robert Moses 1888-1981, Coordinator of 'Limited Objectives' by Gerard Malanga...", undated (Box 94 (Oversize))
  - "Bill Berkson Folder", undated (Box 94 (Oversize))
  - " This Will Kill That, Research for Cover...", undated (Box 94 (Oversize))
  - "Simon Federman, 'The Gift'", undated (Box 94 (Oversize))
  - Printed material, undated; 2 (Box 94 (Oversize))
  - Pressbook, undated (Box 95 (Oversize))
  - Film stills and photographs, undated; 3 (Box 96 (Oversize))
  - Benno Friedman photographs, 1975-1979 (Box 97 (Oversize))
  - Collaborations, undated (Box 97 (Oversize))
  - "Scopophilia" material, undated; 3 (Box 97 (Oversize))
  - "Angus MacLise Artwork / Calligraphy", undated (Box 98 (Oversize))
  - "Associated with DIA: Full Pg Ad & Poem Appreances by Rene Ricard...", undated (Box 98 (Oversize))
  - "Photocopy Delineation. GM's 'Pictures'", circa 1994 (Box 98 (Oversize))
  - "Assortment of Posters, Incl. Signed Malanga Poster", undated (Box 98 (Oversize))
  - "Xecutioners Silkscreen Poster...", undated (Box 98 (Oversize))
  - "Kahlil Gibson Proofs for Installation", undated (Box 99 (Oversize))
  - "Angus MacLise Original Artwork Calligraphy & Holograph of Poem", undated (Box 99 (Oversize))
  - Photographs, undated (Box 99 (Oversize))
  - "Lou Lou de la Falaise" clippings, undated (Box 99 (Oversize))
  - " Autobiography of a Sex Thief, Final Draft Dummy", undated (Box 99 (Oversize))
  - Printed material, undated; 4 (Box 100 (Oversize))
  - "Highbridge Pool Twenty Times," Polaroid 47 film, photo-plastique by GM (See: GM/Paul Bang file), 1986 (Box 101 (Art))
  - Framed photo-illustrations, undated (Box 102 (Art))
  - Poster, undated (Box 103 (Roll))
  - Poster, undated (Box 104 (Roll))
  - Poster, undated (Box 105 (Roll))
  - Poster, undated (Box 106 (Roll))
  - Poster, undated (Box 107 (Roll))
  - Poster, undated (Box 108 (Roll))
  - "The Cooler" posters, undated (Box 109 (Broadside Oversize))
  - Designs relating to Robert Moses, Tompkins Square Park, and the pool exhibit, undated (Box 110 (Broadside Oversize))
  - Posters, undated (Box 111 (Broadside Oversize))
  - "Commemorative Ltd Edtn Poster. G.M. Exhibit, Tokyo, Japan", 2003 (Box 112 (Broadside Oversize))
  - Audiovisual Materials, undated; (11 audiocassettes, 1 7" reel to reel tape, 1 VHS videocassette) (Box 113)
    Restricted fragile material. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
    - Henry Moore / Richard Aaron, 1980 December 5; 1 (Box 113, Item barcode 39002091394180)
      There are associated papers contained in two folders in box 4 under the title "Richard Aaron/Henry Moore".
    - Gerard Malanga phone interview by Maria Massey for Vagabond, 1989 October 12; 1 (Box 113, Item barcode 39002091394198)
      Extensive notes related to this audiocassette is housed in Box 16 under the title: "Gerard Malanga Interview for Vagabond (Ed. Bob Putnam, St. Louis - Oct. 12, 1989)".
    - Vincent Fremont / Turnbun Colver...(1 of 2 cassettes), 1990 April 6-June 27; 1 (Box 113, Item barcode 39002091394206)
      Contents written on the label include names and dates.
      Vincent Fremont, 4/6/90
      Turnbun Colver, 4/13/90
      Robert Creely, 5/23/90
      Tracey Tillett, 5/23/90
      Tracey Tillett, 5/29/90
      2 Calls, 5/30/90
      Anita Pallenberg, 6/13/90
      Tracey Tillett, 6/19/90
      Tracey Tillett, 6/23
      Tracey Tillett, 6/24
      Tracey Tillett, 6/27
    - The Cloud Doctrine / Clarion of I / Diane Di / M M (2 of 2 cassettes), 1981 March 8; 1 (Box 113, Item barcode 39002091394214)
      Contents written on the cassette label includes "Noon Rose" birth.
    - "The G and VV Story" with Ira Cohen and Gerard Malanga", phone conversation, 1993 March 10-11; 1 (Box 113, Item barcode 39002091394222)
      Information on the label describes the contents as telephone messages on Gerard Malanga's answering machine from Ira Cohen. Cohen discusses Malanga's filmscript "Talking Pictures".
      Detailed notes associated with this audiocassette are housed in box 42 under "The G and VV Story..."
    - Readings of Julia to Gerard, Letters of Commentary and Footnotes and Affectionate Whispers (1 of 4 cassettes), 1985 September 18-October 7; 1 (Box 113, Item barcode 39002091394230)
    - Julia #2 17 x 85, with Love and Kisses (2 of 4 cassettes), undated; 1 (Box 113, Item barcode 39002091394248)
    - J 2 G #3 (3 of 4 cassettes), undated; 1 (Box 113, Item barcode 39002091394255)
      A handwritten note included with the audiocassette states 'Poem cut off on B side'. It reads: The savage is reborn within himself, within the civilized he needs anarchy in projected order. He needs his life back. He's been denied, hidden molded kicked goaded stripped driven and he's back here now always cannot be killed but he can kill wants blood yours.
    - Julia #4 2 Gerard (4 of 4 cassettes), 1985 October 22; 1 (Box 113, Item barcode 39002091394263)
    - "Andy Warhol" by Gerard Malanga, interview Scopophilia, 1982 March 9; 1 (Box 113, Item barcode 39002091394271)
      Paperwork associated with this audiocassette is located in box 47 under "Scopophilia correspondance and ephemera".
    - "Mike Donnelly" by Gerard Malanga, interview Scopophilia, 1982 March 30; 1 (Box 113, Item barcode 39002091394289)
      Paperwork connected with this audiocassette can be found in box 47 under "Scopophilia correspondence and ephemera".
    - Patti Smith poetry reading, recorded and produced by Gerard Malanga, 1971 February 10; 1 (Box 113, Item barcode 39002091394297)
      This audiotape reel has corresponding papers stored in five folders in box 55 titled: Patti Smith material. The reel's speed is listed as 3 3/4 ips. The venue is listed as St. Mark's in-the-Bouwerie.
    - Notes on Marie Menken by Martina Kudlácek, undated; 1 (Box 113, Item barcode 39002091394305)
  - Electronic Media, undated; (2 CDs, 1 DVD) (Box 114)
    Restricted fragile material. Reference copies of computer disks may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
- September 2006 acquisition, 1971-2006; 1.59; (4 boxes)
  The September 2006 Addition includes audiocassettes and reel-to-reel sound recordings, drafts of writings, printed material, and ephemera.
  Former call number: Uncat MSS 960.
  - Audiovisual Material
    Restricted fragile material. Reference copies of may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - David Rosenberg poet and early publisher of Malanga's work in The Ant's Forefoot (1 of 2 cassettes), undated; 1 (Box 115, Item barcode 39002091394016)
      This audiocassette is a taped conversation with Gerard Malanga on the subject of the kaballah and its relationship to poetry.
    - David Rosenberg poet and early publisher of Malanga's work in The Ant's Forefoot (2 of 2 cassettes), undated; 1 (Box 115, Item barcode 39002091394024)
    - "Black Box 9" (1 of 2 cassettes), 1976; 1 (Box 115, Item barcode 39002091394032)
    - "Black Box 9" (2 of 2 cassettes), 1976; 1 (Box 115, Item barcode 39002091394040)
    - Gerard Malanga, "The Body Politic", Chicago, 1973 May 28; 1 (Box 115, Item barcode 39002091394057)
      This reading was given by Gerard Malanga during a one-week stopover while in transit via a bus from San Francisco to Lenox, MA.
    - "For Gerard", 1984; 1 (Box 115, Item barcode 39002091394065)
    - "Gerard Malanga Reading His Poems", undated; 1 (Box 115, Item barcode 39002091394073)
    - "The Ridgewood Tape", 1986 June; 1 (Box 115, Item barcode 39002091394081)
      A note reads: For Gerard, Some pretty songs from the Magic Land. WCS
    - "First Annual Radiothon for the Old Poets' Home", undated; 1 (Box 115, Item barcode 39002091394099)
      This cassette was taped in stereo. A runtime reads: 26:44.
    - GM: David Ignatow Paris Review Interview & Tapes (1 of 4 cassettes), 1975 March 28; 1 (Box 115, Item barcode 39002091394107)
    - GM: David Ignatow Paris Review Interview & Tapes (2 of 4 cassettes), 1975 March 28; 1 (Box 115, Item barcode 39002091394115)
    - GM: David Ignatow Paris Review Interview & Tapes (3 of 4 cassettes), 1975 January 31; 1 (Box 115, Item barcode 39002091394123)
    - GM: David Ignatow Paris Review Interview & Tapes (4 of 4 cassettes), 1975 January 31; 1 (Box 115, Item barcode 39002091394131)
    - Anne Waldman, undated; 1 (Box 115, Item barcode 39002091394149)
    - Charles Simic, undated; 1 (Box 115, Item barcode 39002091394156)
    - Allen de Loach, "The Poetry Project", 1971 April 6; 1 (Box 115, Item barcode 39002091394164)
    - Shirley Kaufman, undated; 1 (Box 115, Item barcode 39002091394172)
    - "Gerard Malanga's Film Notebooks", circa 2005 (Box 116 (Oversize))
    - "Uwe [Hauslein?] Wooden Box Ltd. Edtn.", undated; (1 folder, 1 audiocassette) (Box 117 (Oversize))
      - Big Brother and the Holding Company, 1993; 1 (Box 117 (Oversize), Item barcode 39002091394537)
        The contents of this audiocassette are listed below.
        Side A / Side B
        1. Ball & Chain, 7:16
        2. Piece of my Heart, 4:40
        1. Women is Losers, 4:34
        2. Fley with me, 3:02
        Box 117 contains audiovisual material and is considered restricted fragile.
  - Other Material
    - David Ignatow interview, printed version, 1979 (Box 118)
    - Printed material, 2006 (Box 118)
    - "Malanga Poetry Reading... Live in Hell's Gate...", 1992 (Box 118)
    - "'South of Heaven,' revised screeplay by Howard Rodman," fourth draft revised, 1990 August 6 (Box 118)
    - "Keith Haring Invites You to the Second Annual 'Party of Life' at the Paladium...", undated (Box 118)
- November 2007 acquisition, 1970-2007; 0.46; (2 boxes) + 2 broadside folders
  Gift of Asako Kitaori and Gerard Malanga, 2007.
  The November 2007 Acquisition includes twenty-two audiocassettes, a page proof of Chelsea 36, one black-and-white photograph of an unidentified child, inscribed to Malanga from Sally Mann, and printed material.
  Former call number: Uncat MSS 990.
  - Audiovisual Material
    - Michael Benedikt, the poetry room at Harvard's Lamont Library, 1978 December 12; 1 (Box 119, Item barcode 39002091394313)
    - Michael Benedikt, poetry reading with selections from The Body, Sky and The Badminton at Gt. Barrington, 1983 April 20; 1 (Box 119, Item barcode 39002091394321)
      The readings were for the Cooper Union "Forum" series in NYC.
    - Michael Benedikt at the Library of Congress, "Retrospective in Mini-Form", 1986 March 4; 1 (Box 119, Item barcode 39002091394339)
    - "Mole Notes" (selections): Michael Benedikt at B.U., 1978 November 8; 1 (Box 119, Item barcode 39002091394347)
    - Michael Benedikt class of April 16, 1 (Box 119, Item barcode 39002091394354)
    - Michael Benedikt selections from The Badminton at Great Barrington reading at PCCC, Paterson, NJ, 1985 October 18; 1 (Box 119, Item barcode 39002091394362)
      Also included on the audiocassette, "Truckers and Literary Intellectual" and "Styles of Orgasm"
    - Michael Benedikt, Song settings by He[berk] etc., 1979; 1 (Box 119, Item barcode 39002091394370)
    - J J Sheswin, 1981 August 18; 1 (Box 119, Item barcode 39002091394388)
    - Jane Shore at Michael Benedikt's class at Boston University, 1979 February 14; 1 (Box 119, Item barcode 39002091394396)
      This audiocassettes notes three new poems.
    - Michael Benedikt poetry reading, Drake University, 1979 October 16; 1 (Box 119, Item barcode 39002091394404)
      Selections in this reading include: The Body Sky, The Badminton at Great Barrington, and Gerald Fenchel.
    - Michael Benedikt work tape, for Library of Congress reading, 1986 January - March 4; 1 (Box 119, Item barcode 39002091394412)
      There are several poems listed on the cassette. They are included below.
      Intro
      "The Tanzaka Troupe"
      "Of Seals, and Our Smiles"
      "Of the Grauly"
      "The Proper [?] of Dealing with People Who Are Heading for Eternity"
      "Negative Re[?] for [?]"
      "To Laura in the 1/2 Lite"
      "Of Sexual Styles"
    - Michael Benedikt at the New England Poetry Club, 1978 May 1; 1 (Box 119, Item barcode 39002091394420)
    - Michael Benedikt reading his poetry at Boston University, 1975 October 27; 1 (Box 119, Item barcode 39002091394438)
    - Michael Benedikt The Prose Poem reading, 1988 November 14; 1 (Box 119, Item barcode 39002091394446)
      The cassette was recorded as part of "Poets + Performers". It includes an introduction by Anne-Marie Levine and includes readings of Mole Notes and Night Cries
    - MB Tests, undated; 1 (Box 119, Item barcode 39002091394453)
      Contents on this audiocassette includes the following: "Hello Michael", "Hi Mom", "Ram", and "Helen".
    - Michael Benedikt poetry reading at Harvard University, 1978 December 12; 1 (Box 119, Item barcode 39002091394461)
    - "Alice's Origins", Zekie Poems, Letter to Everybody on Earth, 1978 September 27; 1 (Box 119, Item barcode 39002091394479)
    - Michael Benedikt poetry workshop at Boston University, 1979 February 28; 1 (Box 119, Item barcode 39002091394487)
    - Reading by Michael Benedikt for Phi Beta Kappa at Brown University, 1979 March 28; 1 (Box 119, Item barcode 39002091394495)
    - Michael Benedikt at Wilkes College, Pennsylvania, 1977; 1 (Box 119, Item barcode 39002091394503)
      The contents of this audiocassette includes: The Body, Sky, Night Cries, and The Badminton at Great Barrington.
    - Michael Benedikt selections from The Badminton at Great Barrington for Poetry Society of America at "The Mansion", Roslyn, Long Island, 1981 November; 1 (Box 119, Item barcode 39002091394511)
      L. L. Zeiger provides the introduction.
    - Poetry reading by Michael Benedikt with selections from The Body, Sky, and The Badminton at Great Barrington at New Canaan Library in Connecticut, 1983 Febrary 20; 1 (Box 119, Item barcode 39002091394529)
  - Other Material
    - Printed material, 2007; 2 (Box 120)
    - Photograph of unidentified child, inscribed by Sally Mann, undated (Box 121 (Broadside))
    - Chelsea 36 table of contents, proof, undated (Box 122 (Broadside))
- November 2007 acquisition, undated; 1
  Gift of Asako Kitaori, 2007.
  The November 2007 Addition consists of a single, framed black-and-white photograph, "Candy Darling's Last Hurrah to Hollywood."
  Former call number: Uncat MSS 994.
  - "Candy Darling's Last Hurrah to Hollywood," black and white photograph, signed and framed, undated (Box 123 (Art))
- July 2008 acquisition, 1970-1997; 2; (2 boxes)
  Gift of Asako Kitaori, 2008.
  The July 2008 Acquisition consists of production or subject files containing negatives and contact sheets with images of people photographed by Malanga.
  Former call number: Uncat MSS 1032.
  - "Great Barrington Environs", 1990
  - "Kung-I 'I-I' Wang", 1990
  - "Anu Vikram", 1997
  - "Allison Hayes", 1995
  - "Sheep Meadow, C.P. / Shana on Skates", 1987
  - "Street & Beach Voyeurism - Sheep Meadow, Central Pk / Compo Beach Window Mannequin", 1987
  - "Couple on Shell Beach, Shelter Is. Isabel, au pair", 1987
  - "Sara Dixon (on a Jim Clyne Shoot [16: ix: 88] + Nixon Quote)", 1988
  - "Origami", 1985
  - "Street Voyeurism (21: iv: 85)", 1985
  - "East 10th Street Fair, Shot w/ Leica", 1983
  - "Mannequin without Hair", 1985
  - "#1 Susan Hanger", 1970 (Box 124)
  - "#2 Cristina Miller in Chadsford, Pa", 1970
  - "#3 Melinda DeHaven", 1970
  - "#4 Martine & Mercedes Visiting the Warhol Factory", 1970
  - "#6 The Sidewinders, NYC", 1970
  - "#7 Wren de Antonio, Paris", 1970
  - "#8 Germany", undated
  - "#9 Joanne Hart, Paris", 1970
  - "#10 Jim Haynes / Norma Moriceau, 1970, London"
  - "#11 Joanna Shimkus off Movie Screen - NYC", 1970
  - "#12 Willie Frankfurt NYC Ballet School", 1971
  - "#13 Andrea Fernandez-Salvador, NYC", 1971
  - "#14 Elizabeth Walker, NYC, Tony Pinck & Cousin Toby", 1971
  - "#15 Patrick O'Neal, Tony Pinck, NYC", 1971
  - "#17 Tony Pinck (Flying to Martha's Vineyard) & Gerard", 1971
  - "#18 Jim Hanafy / Bob Colacello / Bob Feiden (Jim Hanafy & Lennie)", 1971
  - "#19 Tristan Baum, NYC (Timothy Baum's 1st Son)", 1971
  - "#21 Jennifer Lee, Nudes (Mrs. Richard Pryor)", 1971
  - "#22 Jenny Fraily", 1971
  - "#23 Candy Clark / Jane Forth Fashion Show", 1971
  - "#24 Paul Caruso / Sag Harbor (The Bob Dylan Lookalike)", 1971
  - "#27 Halston Fashion Show w/ Berry Berenson Taking Pictures, NYC", 1971
  - "#28 Unidentified Girl, Misc.", 1971
  - "#29 Sam Greene, Peter Knoll", 1971
  - "#30 Buddy Wirtschafter / Southampton Beach & Gerard Malanga", 1971
  - "#31 Suzie & Friend (Friends of Terry Ork)", 1971
  - "#32 Art Deco Textile Patterns, Metropolitan Museum of Art Collection", 1971
  - "#33 Bob Rudnick / John McCormick", 1971
  - "#34 Robert Feiden, NYC", 1971
  - "#35 Patrick O'Neal, NYC", 1971
  - "#36 Leigh Taylor-Young w/ Son, Patrick O'Neal", 1971
  - "#37 Leigh Taylor-Young, Son Sean O'Neill / Mark Saunders & Stephen Mueller, Amy Sullivan", 1971
  - "#38 Derek Romley, Architect, & Boyfriend", 1971
  - "#40 Francesca Kress, NYC, & Boyfriend", 1971
  - "#41 Michael Reynolds, Artist. Houses in Weston, Mass.", 1973
  - "#42 Ruby Lynne Rainer, NYC", 1974
  - "#43 Cars & Guitars", 1971
  - "#44 Indian Players / Musicians", 1971
  - "#45 Unidentified (Jennifer Lee's Friend)", 1971
  - "#46 Paris Environs", 1972
  - "#47 Nicoletta Michiavelli, Actor, London", 1972
  - "#48 Sally James, London", 1972
  - "#49 Lila, a Play", 1972
  - "#50 Landscape - on the Road", 1972
  - "#51 Landscape, Texas", 1972
  - "#52 Landscape, Mexico", 1972
  - "#53 Naples, Italy, Louis Waldon", 1972
  - "#54 Eileen Taft, Intransit", 1972
  - "#55 Eileen Taft, Houston, Texas / Tres Vidas, Acapulco, Mexico", 1972
  - "#56 Eileen Taft w/ Daisy Aldan, Outside Serendipity", 1972
  - "#57 Eileen Taft, Alford, Mass.", 1972
  - "#58 Alford House, Exterior", 1972
  - "#59 Liz Leonard in Driveway of Alice's Restaurant, Housatonic, Mass.", 1973
  - "#60 Benno Friedman on Lawnmower / Degan Snyder", 1973
  - "#61 Herb Caen & Marcy Grace, S.F.", 1973
  - "#62 The Sidewinders", 1973
  - "#63 Adrian Brooks", 1974
  - "#64 Caroly (Davis) McWorter & Chris Young in the Berkshires", 1978
  - "#65 Marisa Berenson, NYC", 1974
  - "#66 Judith Mandelbaum, Poet", 1974
  - "#67 Charlene Seeger & Family", 1974
  - "#68 Leon Brocktin", 1976
  - "#69 S.R. Lavin & Music Group at the 5 Spot, NYC", 1976
  - "#70 Dana Buckley - Engagement Party", 1975
  - "#71 Poets-in-the-Schools Program", 1975
  - "#72 Kathy Deiner, Fairport, NY", 1975
  - "#73 Sylvie Texier, NYC", 1975
  - "#74 Sandy Miller & Louis Waldon in Staten Island", 1975
  - "#75 Judith Mandelbaum, Poet", 1975
  - "#76 Sheri Sussman, Poet", 1975
  - "#77 Adrian Brooks, Poet", 1976
  - "#78 Billy Sullivan, Painter (Out-of-focus Roll), Sylvie Texier, NYC", 1976
  - "#79 Belinda Aberbach, L.I. and Gerard Malanga", 1976
  - "#80 Patricia Dow, Fashion Model", 1976
  - "#81 Bobbie Bristol Gladstone Weekend", 1976
  - "#82 Deborah Friedman, NYC", 1976
  - "#83 David Finnegan / Deborah Glazer Stokes House, Bennington College", 1980
  - "#84 Deborah Glazer, Bennington College", 1980
  - "#85 Claire Burchert, Student, Bennington College, Paul Bang", 1980
  - "#86 Bennington College July Program. Jazel Glick (Dr. Anna Glick's Daughter) / Paul Bang", 1980
  - "#87 Karin Strandjord, Actress, NYC", 1980
  - "#88 Jeff Goldberg / Suzan Cooper", 1980
  - "#89 Mimi Theresa Lutz, NYC", 1980
  - "#90 Lenny DiPierre, Actor", 1980
  - "#91 Wendell McAnuff, Actress", 1980
  - "#92 Andrine Ross (re-shoot) East Hampton, John Herssy, Jr.", 1980
  - "#93 The Quarry, W. Stockbridge. Jana Johnston's Knee", 1980
  - "#94 David Finnegan, Bennington College", 1980
  - "#95 Tricia Mahlow, Cannon Hersey's Nanny", 1980
  - "#96 Baird Hersey in Concert, Battery Park", 1980
  - "#97 Claudia Sloan, NYC, & Gerard Malanga - Green River", 1980
  - "#98 Caroly MacWhorter / Liza Stelle", 1980
  - "#100 Adam & Margaret Cumbie, East Hampton, NY, L.I.", 1979 July 2
  - "#101 June Clark & Daughter, The Berkshires", 1978
  - "#102 Sarah Wainwright / David Daio Exhibit", 1978 (Box 125)
  - "#103 Kate Lynn, NYC", 1978 (Box 125)
  - "#104 Unidentified Businessmen, New York Magazine Spec Shoot", 1978 (Box 125)
  - "#105 Fashion Shoot, Bethesda Fountain, Central Pk.", 1987 (Box 125)
  - "#106 Dale Davis / Catherine Davis", 1978 (Box 125)
  - "#107 Maureen & Joe's Wedding at John Hersey's Home, Millbrook, NY", 1981 (Box 125)
  - "#108 Renee Graubert, Nancy Kulp, Millbrook, NY", 1981 (Box 125)
  - "#109 Ellie Brooks, NYC", 1981 (Box 125)
  - "#110 Louis Chaban & Friend, & Gerard Malanga", 1978 (Box 125)
  - "#111 Lyne Talbordet & Paul Bang, NYC", 1982 (Box 125)
  - "#112 Jeanne Oliver & Jessie", 1982 (Box 125)
  - "#113 Cori Jones & Friend, Dog Bite Scar, East Hampton, NY", 1982 (Box 125)
  - "#114 Jennifer Boin, Hoboken, NJ / Street Voyeurism", 1982 (Box 125)
  - "#115 Leslie Beadle, Riding Stable", 1982 (Box 125)
  - "#116 MISA (Manhattan Island Swimming Assn) w/ Hoe, Drury Gallagher / Benson Haggard, NYC", 1982 (Box 125)
  - "#117 Phil Bleeth & Jane Pittman, Claremont Stables, NYC", 1982 (Box 125)
  - "#118 Whitney de Lise, Actress", 1982 (Box 125)
  - "Volleyball Voyeurism, Washington Square Park", 1982 (Box 125)
  - "Southampton Beaches", 1982 (Box 125)
  - "Karen Sweney / Street Voyeurism, Novelist", 1982 (Box 125)
  - "#119 Jeanne Oliver's Sister, Jessie, NYC", 1982 (Box 125)
  - "#120 Brooklyn Bridge Swim", 1983 (Box 125)
  - "#121 Saskia Dell & Daughter, Sabina, NYC", 1983 (Box 125)
  - "#121A Phoebe Sudrow, 23:iv:83 (Suzie Perry, Lexie Bilancia, Bard College, 22:iv:83)", 1983 (Box 125)
  - "#122 Agneta Eckemyr Fashion Show, NYC", 1983 (Box 125)
  - "#123 Zoe Van DeWiele, NYC", 1983 (Box 125)
  - "#124 Bill & Julie Plikaitis w/ Daughter Kate, Middletown, CT", 1983 (Box 125)
  - "#125 Suzanne & Charlie Stephans (Suzanne, Wife of Dustin Pittman) - L.I.", 1984 (Box 125)
  - "#126 Meredith Novak, NYC", 1984 (Box 125)
  - "#127 Alix Michel & Her Horse (#83184)", 1984 (Box 125)
  - "#128 Capital Projects / Flushing Meadow Park, NYC", 1985 (Box 125)
  - "#129 Carmine Street Recreation Center, NYC", 1985 (Box 125)
  - "#130 Kelly Jo Schwinghammer, Model, NYC", 1985 May 8 (Box 125)
  - "#131 Michael Siegel, NYC Parks Historian", 1985 (Box 125)
  - "#132 Jennifer Cromley & Her Brother, Seth, NYC", 1985 (Box 125)
  - "#133 Belvedere Castle, Central Park, NYC", 1985 (Box 125)
  - "#134 Riverside Park Clean-up, NYC", 1985 (Box 125)
  - "#135 Ribbon Rock, Harlem River Drive, NYC", 1985 (Box 125)
  - "#136 National Resources / Park Ranger Program, NYC", 1985 (Box 125)
  - "#137 Charles McKinny, Dir. of Riverside Pk / 79th Street Rotunda, NYC", 1985 (Box 125)
  - "#138 Wendy Valentine, Say Magazine", 1986 (Box 125)
  - "#139 Union Sq. Park Restoration", 1986 (Box 125)
  - "#140A - Gerard, East Hampton / Bathhouse, Bklyn", 1987 (Box 125)
  - "#141 Kristen Johnson", 1987 (Box 125)
  - "#142 Shelter Island, Bill & Julie Plikaitis", 1987 (Box 125)
  - "#143 SPLASH Magazine Shoot w/ Valerie, Model. Reject Shots", 1989 (Box 125)